There once
was a peculiar doctor,
known for
his extraordinary ability.
He could talk to animals.
Dr. Dolittle's reputation
spread far and wide.
Even the Queen of England
called on him.
So grateful for his help,
she gifted him
a wondrous sanctuary
whose doors were open
to all creatures.
His days belonged
to the animals,
but his heart
belonged to one woman,
Lily, the fearless explorer.
They traveled the globe,
going on great adventures.
Defending creatures
who could not defend themselves.
They made
an extraordinary team.
Soon, that team
became a family.
With Lily by his side,
Dolittle never felt more alive.
Until one day,
she left on an adventure.
Lily died at sea.
Heartbroken,
he locked
the gates of the manor
and completely retreated
from the world.
As for me, and the animals
whose lives he'd saved,
we were left to wonder,
could anyone save his?
Until one morning,
a most unlikely creature
found its way
into Dolittle's life.
A very special boy.
In a time where people
thought of animals
only as possessions,
food, or sport,
this boy felt
quite differently.
This way,
me scattered squirrel.
Right.
Junior flushes them.
You shoot them, yeah?
Right.
Good plan, Dad.
Get ready.
Shoulder your gun.
Do I have to, Uncle?
Come on, boy.
Duck! Duck!
Duck, duck, duck!
There, there they go.
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
You got him, you got him, you got him.
Oh, no, I can't!
Shoot,
shoot, shoot.
You can't keep
missing on purpo