Go on.
Go on and be gone!
I don't care about anyone,
anything, anywhere anymore.
The birds
will show you out.
Right,
everything's tidy.
Lunch will be served
in a minute, now.
Mmm!
Smells lovely, Doc.
Thanks very much.
Hey, Doc,
save some for us this time.
Sorry, Doc.
Guess I'm scared of kids, too.
Don't worry about that.
Come on, let's eat.
I'm going to be offering
today a brothy soup.
You'll never believe
what we caught in the net.
The queen has asked
for you by name, sir.
Are you hard of hearing?
I told you
I'm closed for business.
What business?
Treating humans.
Intruder alert!
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Well, I'm not.
My house is descending
into chaos.
Is he yours?
I don't own anybody.
Yoshi had an issue
that he came to me with.
He's always cold.